usetallie.com 2015-03-17

# Expense Report Software Privacy Policy | Tallie

#### What does this privacy policy cover?

This Privacy Policy covers SpringAhead's treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that SpringAhead gathers when you access the Website and when you use SpringAhead's services or applications. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that SpringAhead does not own or control, or to individuals that SpringAhead does not employ or manage. 

#### Personal Information You Provide to Us

We may receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected include your full name, email address, IP address, browser information, username, password and any other information necessary for us to provide our services. 

#### Personal Information Collected Automatically

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Website or use our services. SpringAhead automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. 

Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Website and its components. SpringAhead only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. 

#### Contact Information

Feel free to contact us for any reason, including a request to be added to or taken off an email list, or if you have any questions or concerns. Please provide your company's name in addition to your name and title. 

**BY POSTAL MAIL**  
525 Second Street.  
San Francisco, CA 94107

**BY PHONE**  

**BY EMAIL**  

#### Communications from SpringAhead

**TO UNSUBSCRIBE FROM SPRINGAHEAD EMAIL**  
If for any reason you would like to unsubscribe from our marketing and promotional email programs, simply click the Unsubscribe link provided at the bottom of the email you receive OR send us an email at [support@springahead.com](mailto:support@springahead.com)

If you no longer wish to receive administrative and customer-service-related email messages, you must deactivate your SpringAhead account. If you are not the administrator of your SpringAhead account, please consult your account Administrator for updating or removing your account. 

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

SpringAhead may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used.
